## Laxman Koli

Katraj, Pune 411046 7875440022 Koli.laxman51@gmail.com

# **Objective**

Highly analytical and process-oriented Data Analyst with in-depth knowledge of database types; research methodologies; and big data capture, curation, manipulation and visualization. Proficient in identifying efficiencies and problem areas within data streams, while communicating needs for projects.

### **Skills**

- Advance Excel: Countifs, Sumifs, Sum product, Mid, Vlookup, Hlookup Pivot Table Index,Indirect,Conditional Formatting.
- Power BI: Calculated Columns, Measures, Modelling & DAX, Visualization, Relationships,
  Power Query.
- Large Data Analysis and Managing Reports
- Creating systems

# **Experience**

07/2021 - Present

#### Data Analyst - Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd.

- Assisted with day-to-day operations, working efficiently and productively with all team members.
- Produced monthly reports using advanced Excel spreadsheet functions, VLOOKUP, Pivot Table HLOOKUP.
- Developed customized reports, summarizing and presenting data in visually appealing format.
- Worked on Power BI with different data sources such as SQL Server using Live Connections as well as importing data from Excel Sources.
- Experience on understanding DAX functions in Power BI and created New columns and New Measures using DAX
- Provide forecasting on daily, weekly, monthly and yearly basis capacity planning.
- Good experience on creating Filters like Visual level, page level, Drill through and Report level filter in Power BI.

10/2017 - 07/2021

#### Manager - CTNL Broadband, Pune

- Coordination with other departments (like product, NOC, call center, sales etc..) for efficient and smooth working.
- Monitor and evaluate business problems, develop process solutions and system requirements.
- Set the milestones and initiate daily/weekly/monthly reports to management.
- New connectivity plan and getting permission from society.
- Shortlist and manage data for other teams.
- Manage inventory data in Excel spreadsheet functions.

04/2013 - 06/2016.

#### Electrical Supervisor - Samruddhi Jeevan Foods India Limited Pune.

- Technical team management
- To shout the complaint of all electrical
- Filling the log sheet of Lt Penal
- Weekly Round in all branch office.

## **Education**

Class	Year of Passing	Marks	Collage/University
B.A.	06/2017	50.11%	Abasaheb Garware College, Pune
HSC	06/2011	47%	Sane Guruji Vidyalay, Pune
ITI	01/2009	Pass	Kohinoor Institute, Wai, Satara.
SSC	06/2008	43%	Shri Shivaji Vidyalay, Surur, Satara.

# **Languages Known**

English, Hindi, Marathi

Place: Pune LAXMAN KOLI